jooria.com 2013-04-03

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction

This statement discloses the privacy practices for **Jooria Refresh Your Website**. this website respects the privacy and rights of its visitors. We do not collect personal identifiable data, and therefore protect user privacy. No effort is made to identify individuals without their knowledge. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

## Ad Networks

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please review their policies. 

We use the following advertising networks: 

  * Google Adsense ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

## Especially Google Adsense Privacy Policy

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## Links to external sites

**Jooria Refresh Your Website** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  

## have a question?

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this policy, please feel free to [contact us.](http://www.jooria.com/contact/)
